AoM Records 5593
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series I. ADMINISTRATIVE RECORDS
  - Sub-Series C. Executive Officers
    - Kast, Fremont, President, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 2)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence RE: Professional Division Policy Committee and Jack Miner
    - Kast, Fremont, President, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 3)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence RE: History, Archives and Library
    - Kast, Fremont, President, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 4)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence with Dennis Ray, Secretary-Treasurer
    - Kast, Fremont, President, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 5)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence with Sigma Iota Epsilon
    - Kast, Fremont, President, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 6)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence RE: Board of Governors Meeting, Spring 1977
    - Kast, Fremont, President, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 7)
      Executive Officer's File, Presidents Address to Southwestern Division of Academy, March 1977
    - Kast, Fremont, President, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 8)
      Executive Officer's File, Presidential Address to Midwest Division, April 1977
    - Kast, Fremont, President, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 9)
      Executive Officer's File, Presidential Address to Eastern Division, Hartford, May 13, 1977
    - Kast, Fremont, President, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 10)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence with Rosemary Pledger RE 1977 Programs
    - Kast, Fremont, President, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 11)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence RE: Local Arrangements Committee for San Francisco
    - Kast, Fremont, President, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Kast, Fremont, President, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence RE: Academy of Management Certificates
    - Kast, Fremont, President, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 2)
      Correspondence RE: Annual Meeting, Kissimmee, FL
    - Kast, Fremont, President, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      Correspondence RE: Business Policy and Planning Division
    - Kast, Fremont, President, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 4)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence RE: Proceedings for 1977, Part I
    - Kast, Fremont, President, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 5)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence RE: Proceedings for 1977, Part II
    - Kast, Fremont, President, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 6)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence RE: Publication Activities
    - Kast, Fremont, President, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 7)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence RE: Soviet Proposition and Other Foreign Exchanges
    - Kast, Fremont, President, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 8)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence RE: Site Selection Activities
    - Kast, Fremont, President, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 9)
      Executive Officer's File, Miscellaneous Letters Received
    - Kast, Fremont, President, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 10)
      Executive Officer's File, Miscellaneous Materials
    - Kast, Fremont, 1977-1979 (Box 43, Folder 11)
      Executive Officer's Files, K3 Committee on Planning
    - LeBreton, Preston, President, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - LeBreton, Preston, President, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - LeBreton, Preston, President, 1965-1966 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - LeBreton, Preston, President, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 4)
      Miscellaneous Correspondence
    - LeBreton, Preston, President, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - LeBreton, Preston, President of Academy, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 6)
      Correspondence RE: Presidential Newsletter
    - LeBreton, Preston, Speech as President Before Academy, "New Directions", 1966 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Litterer, Joseph, President-Elect, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Litterer, Joseph, President, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 9-16)
    - Litterer, Joseph, Miscellaneous Academy of Management Administrative Calendar, 1970-1971 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Mandeville, Merton J., President, 1959 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - McFarland, Dalton, Secretary-Treasurer, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 2-6)
    - McFarland, Dalton, Secretary-Treasurer, 1965 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - McFarland, Dalton, 1965-1968 (Box 45, Folder 8)
      Executive Officer's File, Presidents Newsletter, November 1965-68
    - McFarland, Dalton, Former President, 1965-1982 (Box 45, Folder 9)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence RE: Photos From 1965, Book Awards and the Photos Enclosed, 1982
    - McGuire, Joseph, Vice President of Public Affairs, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Mee, John F., 1936-1949 (Box 45, Folder 11)
      Executive Officers File, Correspondence
    - Mee, John F., 1950-1951 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Mee, John F., 1952 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Mee, John F., 1953 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Mee, John F., 1954 (Box 45a, Folder 1)
    - Mee, John F., 1955 (Box 45a, Folder 2)
    - Mee, John F., 1960 (Box 45a, Folder 3)
    - Mee, John F., 1961 (Box 45a, Folder 4)
    - Mee, John F., 1962-1963 (Box 45a, Folder 5)
    - Mee, John F., 1964 (Box 45a, Folder 6)
    - Mee, John F., 1965 (Box 45a, Folder 7)
    - Mee, John F., 1966-1967 (Box 45a, Folder 8)
    - Mee, John F., 1968-1969 (Box 45a, Folder 9)
    - Mee, John F., 1970-1979 (Box 45a, Folder 10)
    - Mee, John F., 1980-1989 (Box 45a, Folder 11)
    - Miner, John, Vice President, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 1-6)
    - Miner, John, Vice President, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 7-19)
    - Miner, John, President-Elect, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 20-22)
    - Miner, John, President-Elect, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 23-26)
    - Miner, John, President, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 27-30)
    - Miner, John, President, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 1-5)
    - Miner, John, President, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 6)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence RE: Academy relationship with American Assembly of Collegiate Schools of Business
    - Miner, John, President, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 7-23)
    - Miner, John, Past-President, 1978-1979 (Box 47, Folder 24-27)
    - Newson, Walter B., Secretary-Treasurer-Elect, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 28)
      Academy Mailing List
    - Pledger, Rosemary, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      Executive Officer's File, Administrative Records
    - Pledger, Rosemary, Administrative Secretary, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Pledger, Rosemary, Administrative Secretary, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Pledger, Rosemary, Administrative Secretary, 1973-1974 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Pledger, Rosemary, Administrative Secretary, 1973-1974 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Pledger, Rosemary, Administrative Secretary, 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Pledger, Rosemary, Secretary-Treasurer, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Pledger, Rosemary, 1976-1977 (Box 48, Folder 8)
      Executive Officer's File, Program Chairperson Budget, Annual Meeting
    - Pledger, Rosemary, 1977-1979 (Box 48, Folder 9)
      Hotel Contracts
    - Pledger, Rosemary, 1977-1981 (Box 48, Folder 10)
      Correspondence with Fellow
    - Pledger, Rosemary, President, 1977-1978 (Box 48, Folder 11)
      Correspondence RE: Professional Division Policy Committee
    - Pledger, Rosemary, President, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 12)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence RE: Sigma Iota Epsilon
    - Pledger, Rosemary, President-Elect, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 13)
      Correspondence RE: Governance Documents
    - Pledger, Rosemary, President-Elect, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Pledger, Rosemary, President-Elect, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Pledger, Rosemary, President-Elect, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 16)
      Executive Officer's File, Reimbursements
    - Pledger, Rosemary, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 17)
      Executive Officer's File, Presidential Speech, Atlanta, GA
    - Pledger, Rosemary, President, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 18)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence on Presidential Address, Academy of Management
    - Pledger, Rosemary, President, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Pledger, Rosemary, 1978-1979 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      Correspondence RE: Werten Hetch, San Francisco, CA, 1978-79 Convention
    - Pledger, Rosemary, President, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 2)
      Correspondence and Papers RE: Annual Meeting, Atlanta, GA, August 8-11, 1979
    - Pledger, Rosemary, President ACM, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 3)
      Eastern Academy of Management Meeting, Newport, RI, May 10-12, 1978, Correspondence
    - Pledger, Rosemary, President, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 4)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence about the LMDC
    - Pledger, Rosemary, President, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Pledger, Rosemary, President, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 6)
      Executive Officer's File, Reimbursement
    - Pledger, Rosemary, Past-President, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Pledger, Rosemary, Acting Past-President, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Pledger, Rosemary, Past-President, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 9)
      Executive Officer's File, Election Material
    - Pledger, Rosemary, Acting Past-President, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Pledger, Rosemary, Past-President, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Pledger, Rosemary, Past-President, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 12)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence, Management History Division, Comments on Constitution and By-Laws
    - Pledger, Rosemary, Past-President, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 13)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence: Constitution
    - Pledger, Rosemary, Past-President, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 14)
      Executive Officer's File, Awards Correspondence
    - Pledger, Rosemary, Past-President, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 15)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence RE: Election of Officers
    - Porter, Lyman, President, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Porter, Lyman, President, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Richards, Max, Secretary-Treasurer, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 1-5)
    - Richards, Max, Secretary-Treasurer, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 6)
      Executive Officer's File, Address Changes
    - Richards, Max, Vice President, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Richards, Max, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Richards, Max, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Richards, Max, President, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Richards, Max, Presidential Newsletter, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 11)
      Oct-67
    - Richards, Max, President ACM, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Richards, Max, Miscellaneous, The Case of Dennis Ford, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 13)
      Includes correspondence concerning the matters of establishing "standards of conduct, professionalism, ethics and moral requirements" for members
    - Richards, Max, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Richards, Max, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Robb, Seward, Secretary-Treasurer, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 16-18)
    - Robb, Seward, Secretary-Treasurer, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 19)
      Executive Officer's File, Includes Attendance Record of 1970 Convention
    - Robb, Seward, Secretary-Treasurer, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 20-21)
    - Robb, Seward, Secretary-Treasurer, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Robb, Seward, Vice President for Professional Division, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 23)
      Executive Officer's File, Includes information pertaining to newly established divisions
    - Shuman, Ronald B., 1941-1948 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Shuman, Ronald B., 1948 (Box 51, Folder 2)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence RE: The Constitutional Revision RE: Special Construction Committee
    - Shuman, Ronald B., 1949 (Box 51, Folder 3)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence RE: Annual Meeting, New York City, December 30, 1949
    - Shuman, Ronald B., 1950 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Shuman, Ronald B., Executive Committee Member, 1951-1953 (Box 51, Folder 5)
      Executive Committee Member, Correspondence
    - Shuman, Ronald B., 1952 (Box 51, Folder 6)
      Executive Officer's File, Award-Associate Member of the American Institute of Management
    - Shuman, Ronald B., 1954 (Box 51, Folder 7)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence RE: Constitutional Revisions
    - Shuman, Ronald B., 1954 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Shuman, Ronald B., 1954 (Box 51, Folder 9)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence 1954, Part 2
    - Shuman, Ronald B., 1954 (Box 51, Folder 10)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence RE: Annual Meeting
    - Shuman, Ronald B., 1954 (Box 51, Folder 11)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence: Miscellaneous
    - Shuman, Ronald B., 1955 (Box 51, Folder 12-13)
    - Shuman, Ronald B., Executive Committee Member, 1955 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Shuman, Ronald B., 1955 (Box 52, Folder 1)
      Executive Officer's File, New Members Correspondence
    - Shuman, Ronald B., 1955 (Box 52, Folder 2)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence RE: 1955 Meeting
    - Shuman, Ronald B., Executive Committee Member, 1955 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Shuman, Ronald B., Executive Committee Member, 1956-1957 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Shuman, Ronald B., Executive Committee Member, 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Shuman, Ronald B., Executive Committee Member, 1958 (Box 52, Folder 6)
      Fellows Meeting, December 1958
    - Shuman, Ronald B., Executive Committee Member, 1960 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Shuman, Ronald B., Executive Committee Member, 1961-1962 (Box 52, Folder 8)
      Awards Committee Correspondence
    - Shuman, Ronald B., Executive Committee Member, 1961-1962 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Shuman, Ronald B., Executive Committee Member, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      Annual Meeting, Academy of Management
    - Shuman, Ronald B., Executive Committee Member, 1962-1963 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Shuman, Ronald B., Executive Committee Member, 1964 (Box 52, Folder 12)
      Correspondence: McKinsey Foundation Bk Awards Program
    - Shuman, Ronald B., Executive Committee Member, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      Correspondence: Misuse of Academy Name
    - Shuman, Ronald B., Executive Committee Member, 1969 (Box 52, Folder 14)
      Financial Material RE: Attendance 19th Annual Meeting of Academy
    - Shuman, Ronald B., Executive Committee Member, 1969 (Box 52, Folder 15)
      Correspondence RE: History of Management Committee
    - Shuman, Ronald B., Executive Committee Member, 1971 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Shuman, Ronald B., Executive Committee Member, 1971 (Box 52, Folder 17)
      Correspondence: Constitutional Revision
    - Shuman, Ronald B., 1972 (Box 52, Folder 18)
      Correspondence: Setting up project to honor Ron's contribution to management
    - Shuman, Ronald B., Executive Committee Member, 1970-1972 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Shuman, Ronald B. (Box 52, Folder 20)
      Biographical Sketch
    - Smiddy, Harold, President, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - Steiner, George, Vice President, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 1-2)
    - Steiner, George, President-Elect, 1971 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Steiner, George, President, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 4-10)
    - Steiner, George, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 11)
      Executive Officer's File, Executive Committee Meetings
    - Steiner, George, Past-President, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Steiner, George, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 13)
      Executive Officer's File, Executive Committee, Includes Reports, Correspondence, etc.
    - Steiner, George, 1971-1972 (Box 53, Folder 14)
      Miscellaneous, Academy of Management and the American Management Association, Correspondence, etc. on cooperative interrelationships between AM & AMA; with James Hayes (AMA Pres) with Wolf
    - Steiner, George, 1971-1972 (Box 53, Folder 15)
      Miscellaneous, Organization, Structure, Includes correspondence and diagrams pertaining to the restructuring of the Academy with the establishment of the professional divisions, etc.
    - Summer, Charles, Vice President, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Summer, Charles, President-Elect, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Summer, Charles, President-Elect, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Summer, Charles, President, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 4-8)
    - Terry, George, Secretary-Treasurer, 1959 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Terry, George, Secretary-Treasurer, 1959 (Box 54, Folder 10-11)
    - Terry, George, President, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Terry, George, Former President, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 13)
      Executive Officer's File, Papers delivered 1975 about events in 1961
    - Towle, Joe, Secretary-Treasurer, 1957 (Box 54, Folder 14-19)
    - Towle, Joe, Secretary-Treasurer, 1958 (Box 54, Folder 20-23)
    - Towle, Joe, Vice President, 1959 (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - Vance, Stanley, Vice President and Program Chairman, 1971-1974 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Vance, Stanley, Vice President and Program Chairman, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 2)
      Correspondence RE: Program for 1974 Annual Meeting
    - Vance, Stanley, Vice President, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Vance, Stanley, President, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Vance, Stanley, President, 1975-1976 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Vance, Stanley, President, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Vance, Stanley, President, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Vance, Stanley, Past-President, 1977 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Vance, Stanley, 1975-1977 (Box 55, Folder 9)
      Correspondence RE: Archives for AOM
    - Vance, Stanley (Box 55, Folder 10)
      Miscellaneous Photos (3)
    - Wolf, William, 1967-1971 (Box 56, Folder 1-5)
      Executive Officers File, General Correspondence
    - Wolf, William, 1971-1979 (Box 57, Folder 1-11)
    - Wolf, William (Box 57, Folder 12)
      Academy of International Management
    - Wolf, William (Box 57, Folder 13)
      Academy of Management Review Committee
    - Wolf, William, 1974 (Box 57, Folder 14-15)
      African Seminar
    - Wolf, William (Box 58, Folder 1-3)
    - Wolf, William, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 4)
      Annual Meeting
    - Wolf, William, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Wolf, William, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Wolf, William, 1974-1976 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Wolf, William, 1976 (Box 58, Folder 8-9)
    - Wolf, William, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Wolf, William, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Wolf, William (Box 58, Folder 12)
      Application forms and brochures
    - Wolf, William (Box 58, Folder 13)
      Archives and Library Committee
    - Wolf, William (Box 58, Folder 14)
      CIPM (Council for the International Progress in Management)
    - Wolf, William (Box 58, Folder 15)
      China Seminar
    - Wolf, William (Box 59, Folder 1)
      College of History of Management Thought
    - Wolf, William (Box 59, Folder 2)
      Committee Assignments
    - Wolf, William (Box 59, Folder 3)
      Committee on International Progress
    - Wolf, William (Box 59, Folder 4)
      Constitution and By-Laws
    - Wolf, William (Box 59, Folder 5)
      "Dead" File
    - Wolf, William (Box 59, Folder 6)
      Divisions - General
    - Wolf, William (Box 59, Folder 7-10)
      Division of International Management
    - Wolf, William (Box 59, Folder 11)
      Eastern Division
    - Wolf, William, 1975 (Box 59, Folder 12)
      Election Materials
    - Wolf, William (Box 59, Folder 13)
      Election of Officers
    - Wolf, William (Box 59, Folder 14)
      European Field Studies
    - Wolf, William (Box 60, Folder 1)
      Executive Committee
    - Wolf, William (Box 60, Folder 2-3)
      Fellows
    - Wolf, William (Box 60, Folder 4)
      Finances
    - Wolf, William (Box 60, Folder 5)
      History of Management Thought
    - Wolf, William (Box 60, Folder 6)
      Japanese Itineraries
    - Wolf, William (Box 60, Folder 7-11)
      Japanese Seminar
    - Wolf, William (Box 61, Folder 1)
      Japanese Seminar, Complaint Against Cook-Gauntlett
    - Wolf, William (Box 61, Folder 2)
      Manpower Management Newsletter
    - Wolf, William (Box 61, Folder 3)
      Manpower Management Division
    - Wolf, William (Box 61, Folder 4)
      Management Education and Development Division
    - Wolf, William (Box 61, Folder 5)
      Management History Division
    - Wolf, William (Box 61, Folder 6)
      Managerial Consultation Division
    - Wolf, William (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Wolf, William, 1972 (Box 61, Folder 8)
      New Orleans Meeting
    - Wolf, William (Box 61, Folder 9)
      Nominating Committee
    - Wolf, William (Box 61, Folder 10)
      Organization and Management Theory Division
    - Wolf, William (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Wolf, William (Box 61, Folder 12)
      Organizational Development Division
    - Wolf, William (Box 61, Folder 13)
      Overseas Seminars
    - Wolf, William (Box 62, Folder 1)
      Participant List
    - Wolf, William (Box 62, Folder 2)
      Personnel and Human Resource Division
    - Wolf, William (Box 62, Folder 3)
      Placement Committee
    - Wolf, William (Box 62, Folder 4)
      Policy and Planning Division
    - Wolf, William (Box 62, Folder 5)
      Policy Manual
    - Wolf, William (Box 62, Folder 6)
      Presidential Newsletter
    - Wolf, William (Box 62, Folder 7)
      Production and Operations Management Division
    - Wolf, William (Box 62, Folder 8)
      Professional Division - General
    - Wolf, William (Box 62, Folder 9)
      Program Planning
    - Wolf, William, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 10)
      Reorganization
    - Wolf, William, 1973-1974 (Box 62, Folder 11)
      Roster
    - Wolf, William (Box 62, Folder 12)
      Roster of Female Members
    - Wolf, William (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Wolf, William (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Wolf, William (Box 62, Folder 15)
      Southwest Division
    - Wolf, William (Box 62, Folder 16)
      Vita
    - Wolf, William (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series D. Committee Records
    - Acquisitions Committee, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Ad-Hoc Committee on College Administration, 1969-1971 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Ad-Hoc Committee on College Administration, Proposed Report: Study on University of Tampa Academic Administration, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Ad-Hoc Committee on Divisional Proceedings, 1968 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Advertising Function, Committee on, 1980-1981 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Archive Committee, Recommendation for location of permanent Academy of Management Archives, 1975-1978 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Bowling Green University Search and Screening Committee for University President, 1970 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Budget Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Budget Committee, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Budget Committee - Budget Report, 1980-1981 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Budget Committee, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Committee for the Study of Consulting, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Committee on Committees, 1969-1970 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Committee on Comparative Administration, 1966-1967 (Box 63, Folder 14)
      Includes: position paper of Midwest region subcommittee by Richard Farmer and statement on national decision making
    - Committee on Comparative Administration, 1967 (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Committee on Comparative Administration, 1967 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Committee on Comparative Administration, 1967 (Box 64, Folder 2)
      Preliminary Report of the Comparative Administration Task Force (study of new directions for ACM in reaction to changes in the field)
    - Committee on Comparative Administration, 1967 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Committee on Comparative Administration, 1967 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Committee on Comparative Administration, 1967-1969 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Committee on Comparative Administration, 1967-1968 (Box 64, Folder 6)
      Committee, Final report for 1967, February 1968
    - Committee on Comparative Administration, 1967 (Box 64, Folder 7)
      Task Force, Preliminary Report, December 1967
    - Committee on Comparative Administration, 1968 (Box 64, Folder 8)
      Research Group Solicitation
    - Committee on Comparative Administration, 1967 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Committee on Continuing Education (for professors of management), 1971 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Committee on Education, Report, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Committee on Foreign Divisions (setting up for division), 1971-1972 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Committee on Relationships Between Regional Divisions and the Academy, Report, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 13)